comicartfans.com 2008-12-17

# Comicartfans :: Privacy Policy

| 

| 

At ComicArtFans.com we recognize that privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use our services, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us. 

ComicArtFans.com collects personal information (First Name, Last Name, and Email Address) from you when you register to use this website. We realize that because of the nature of this hobby your privacy is very important to you, particularly when displaying pieces from your collection. Therefore we give you the opportunity to modify your name so it can read however you like. We never display your email address on the site and only allow other site users to contact you through email forms which conceal your email address. 

We will never, under any circumstance, provide your information to another party. 

Periodically we may contact you with promotions or services we feel might be of interest to you. 

**Personal Information**

  * ComicArtFans.com uses cookies and other technologies to enhance your online experience and to learn about how you use ComicArtFans.com services in order to improve the quality of our services. 

**Uses**

  * We may use personal information to provide the services you've requested, including services that display customized content and advertising. 
  * We may also use personal information for auditing, research and analysis to operate and improve ComicArtFans.com technologies and services. 

**Your Choices**

  * You may refuse cookies in your browser, although some of our features or services may not function properly as a result. 
  * We make good faith efforts to provide you access to your personal information upon request and to let you correct such data if it is inaccurate and delete it, when reasonably possible. 

If you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy please Contact Us. 

|    
  
---|---  
  
**COMICARTFANS.COM** |    |  | _**ADDITIONAL EBAY RESOURCES**_  
---  
  
**GALLERIES** | Member Galleries | Most Views | Recent Gallery Updates | Sketchbook | Lowry  
  
**ART FOR SALE** | Classifieds | For Sale Search | Hot eBay Auctions | Member Auctions | Most Popular Comic Art Auctions | Selling? Search All Want Lists!  
  
**RESEARCH/RESOURCES** | Market Data | Popular Comic Art Keywords | News | Create a Qurl  
  
**COMMUNITY** | Chat Room  
**MORE FOR SALE** | Bookstore | Purchase a Portfolio  
**SITE SERVICES** | Site Map | FAQ Sign Up | Log In | Contact Us | Advertise  
  
**Network Sites  

**Hot Ebay Auctions[ VIEW ALL!](http://www.comicartfans.com/ebayauctionshot.asp)**               [**New to eBay? Click Here to Register Now!**](http://rover.ebay.com/rover/1/711-53200-19255-0/1?campid=5335806955&toolid=10001&customid=CAFNewUserSignup&mpre=https%3A%2F%2Fscgi.ebay.com%2Fws%2FeBayISAPI.dll%3FRegisterEnterInfo%26siteid%3D0%26co_partnerid%3D2%26usage%3D0%26ru%3Ddefault)  
---  
Ends: 12/18/2008 9:38:00 AM PDT  |  [](http://rover.ebay.com/rover/1/711-53200-19255-0/1?campid=5335806955&toolid=10001&customid=CAFHotFooter&mpre=http%3A%2F%2Fcgi%2Eebay%2Ecom%2FVAMPIRELLA%2DOriginal%2Dcomic%2Dart%2DPaul%2DAbrams%2DWOW%5FW0QQitemZ250344012605QQcmdZViewItemQQptZLH%5FDefaultDomain%5F0%3Fhash%3Ditem250344012605%26%5Ftrksid%3Dp3286%2Ec0%2Em14%26%5Ftrkparms%3D66%253A2%257C65%253A10%257C39%253A1%257C240%253A1318)  
Ends: 12/21/2008 2:20:00 PM PDT  |  [](http://rover.ebay.com/rover/1/711-53200-19255-0/1?campid=5335806955&toolid=10001&customid=CAFHotFooter&mpre=http%3A%2F%2Fcgi%2Eebay%2Ecom%2FBACHALO%2DMARVEL%2DMASTERPIECES%2DARTISTS%2DPROOF%2DBLACK%2DWIDOW%5FW0QQitemZ170285242434QQcmdZViewItemQQptZLH%5FDefaultDomain%5F0%3Fhash%3Ditem170285242434%26%5Ftrksid%3Dp3286%2Ec0%2Em14%26%5Ftrkparms%3D66%253A2%257C65%253A10%257C39%253A1%257C240%253A1318)  
Ends: 12/22/2008 4:15:00 PM PDT  |  [](http://rover.ebay.com/rover/1/711-53200-19255-0/1?campid=5335806955&toolid=10001&customid=CAFHotFooter&mpre=http%3A%2F%2Fcgi%2Eebay%2Ecom%2FGAIMAN%2DSandman%2DSp%2D1%2Dsplash%2DSandman%2DSon%2DBRYAN%2DTALBOT%5FW0QQitemZ120350287754QQcmdZViewItemQQptZLH%5FDefaultDomain%5F0%3Fhash%3Ditem120350287754%26%5Ftrksid%3Dp3286%2Ec0%2Em14%26%5Ftrkparms%3D66%253A2%257C65%253A10%257C39%253A1%257C240%253A1318)  
Ends: 1/13/2009 1:44:00 PM PDT  |  [](http://rover.ebay.com/rover/1/711-53200-19255-0/1?campid=5335806955&toolid=10001&customid=CAFHotFooter&mpre=http%3A%2F%2Fcgi%2Eebay%2Ecom%2FAvengers%2DCover%2D50%2DCaptain%2DAmerica%2DVision%2Dand%2Dmore%5FW0QQitemZ320325190495QQcmdZViewItemQQptZLH%5FDefaultDomain%5F0%3Fhash%3Ditem320325190495%26%5Ftrksid%3Dp3286%2Ec0%2Em14%26%5Ftrkparms%3D66%253A2%257C65%253A10%257C39%253A1%257C240%253A1318)  
Ends: 12/21/2008 9:03:00 AM PDT  |  [](http://rover.ebay.com/rover/1/711-53200-19255-0/1?campid=5335806955&toolid=10001&customid=CAFHotFooter&mpre=http%3A%2F%2Fcgi%2Eebay%2Ecom%2FMarc%2DHempel%2DSandman%2DOriginal%2DArt%2DMorpheus%2DCorinthian%5FW0QQitemZ330294843018QQcmdZViewItemQQptZLH%5FDefaultDomain%5F0%3Fhash%3Ditem330294843018%26%5Ftrksid%3Dp3286%2Ec0%2Em14%26%5Ftrkparms%3D66%253A2%257C65%253A10%257C39%253A1%257C240%253A1318)  
Ends: 12/22/2008 6:29:00 PM PDT   

All Images & Characters contained within this site are copyright and trademark their respective owners.   
No portion of this web site, including the images contained herein, may be reproduced without the express written permission of the appropriate copyright & trademark holder. 

[Terms and Conditions](http://www.comicartfans.com/signup.asp) for using this web site.   
View our [Privacy Policy](http://www.comicartfans.com/privacypolicy.asp). 

© 2003 - 2008 ComicArtFans.com, All rights reserved.
